Contact

19mba7028@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ iamaindrilachatterjee (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Computational Biology Biophysics Business Analytics

Languages

English (Full Professional)
Bengali (Native or Bilingual)
Hindi (Full Professional)

Certifications

Google Analytics

B and C Certificate of National Cadet Corps

Accounting Fundamentals

The Fundamentals of Digital Marketing

Reading Financial Statements

Aindrila Chatterjee

Future Business Analyst

Chandigarh

Summary

An enthusiastic, hard working, confident, creative personality with down to earth gestures, life values and leadership qualities. Love to live freely and enjoy every bit of life.

I am a Biophysicist and has a master's degree in it. I completed my Bachelors and Masters in Biophysics from Panjab University, Chandigarh. I have also done a research project on Antimicrobial Peptide CATH-2.

Currently I am pursuing MBA in Business Analytics from Chandigarh University.

I am also a NCC Cadet (Air Wing). I also volunteered for Vivo IPL 2018 for King's XI Punjab as a Service Provider.

Experience

INVESTOSURE

Research Analyst and Portfolio management intern June 2020 - July 2020 (2 months)

Digifuse

Marketing And Business Development Intern May 2020 - July 2020 (3 months)

International Centre for Culture & Education Climate Counselor April 2020 - May 2020 (2 months) India

Self Employed
Private Tutor
July 2014 - December 2019 (5 years 6 months)

Chandigarh Area, India

Education

CHANDIGARH UNIVERSITY

Master of Business Administration - MBA, Business Analytics · (2019 - 2021)

Panjab University

Master of Science, Biophysics · (2015 - 2017)

Panjab University

Bachelor of Science - BS, Biophysics · (2012 - 2015)

Kendriya Vidyalaya

· (2000 - 2012)